Guide to the Donald F. Clark Collection circa 1642-1920 MS 118
New-York Historical Society
- Worthington, Asa. Letter to E. Foote. Camp Fredericksburgh, 1778 November 13 (Box 3, Item 424)
  Regarding buckwheat and cattle.
- Mills, Capt. Peter. Receipt. Fishkill Landing, 1778 November 29 (Box 2, Item 255)
- Report of Main Guard. Fort Clinton, 1778 December 14 (Box 1, Item 132)
- Jenkinson, C. Warrant for Augmenting the 60th or Royal American Regiment of Foot, 1778 December 25 (Box 1, Item 55)
- Hanson, Dirick. Military payroll of Captain Dirick Hanson's Company of Colonel James Livingston's Battalion, 1779 January (Box 3, Item 480)
  Original returned, photocopy only
- Clinton, George. Letter. Poughkeepsie, 1779 February 2 (Box 1, Item 61)
- Worthington, Asa. Letter to Ebenezer Foote, 1779 February 6 (Box 5, Item 591)
  Regarding cattle.
- Clinton, George. Letter to Governor Green of Rhode Island. Pokeepsie, NY, 1779 February 13 (Box 1, Item 51)
  Cannot export flour for the relief of the inhabitants of Rhode Island.
- Cramahe, Lieutenant Governor Pay order for Lieutenants Maclean and Howard. Quebec, 1779 February 16 (Box 3, Item 423)
- Kiers, E.M. Letter to Mr. Fisher. Kings Ferry, 1779 February 25 (Box 1, Item 59)
- Clinton, Sir Henry. Letter to Captain Lord George Germain. New York, 1779 February 25 (Box 3, Item 381)
- Livingston, James. Military payroll of Colonel James Livingston's Battalion, 1779 February and March (Box 3, Item 477)
- Scott, John Morin. Memorandum and Reasons of the Secretary of State for granting him a sum of pounds, 1779 March (Box 1, Item 13)
- Robichaux, James. Military payroll of Captain James Robichaux's Company of Colonel James Livingston's Battalion, 1779 March (Box 4, Item 487)
- Livingston, Walter, Speaker of the NY Assembly, 1778-1779. Account receipt. Abraham Brasher. Poughkeepsie, 1779 March 15 (Box 5, Item 568)
- Henry, Robert. Order for white rope to Mr. John Fisher, clothier. Fishkill, 1779 March 31 (Box 2, Item 259)
- Van Rensselaer, Peter. Military payroll of Captain Peter Van Rensselaer's Company of Colonel James Livingston's Battalion, 1779 April (Box 3, Item 483)
- Pixley, Asa. Letter to officer in charge of clothing. West Point, 1779 April 4 (Box 3, Item 421)
  Suit to Captain Abraham Williams.
- Henry, Robert. Order to Mr. John Fisher, clothier. Fishkill, 1779 April 5 (Box 2, Item 258)
- Gansvoort, H. Advance pay to officers. State of Massachusetts Bay, 1779 April 15 (Box 1, Item 134)
  Printed and signed.
- Fernald, Major Tobias. Order on paymaster. West Point, 1779 April 18 (Box 1, Item 98)
- Clinton, Sir Henry. Commission to Captain Cyre Power French. New York, 1779 April 25 (Box 3, Item 382)
  Subsistence warrant.
- Snyder, Colonel John. Letter to Captain Mattys Dederick. Kingston, 1779 April 30 (Box 3, Item 337)
  Scouting party but alarm groundless.
- Livingston, James. Military payroll of Colonel James Livingston's Regiment, 1779 May (Box 3, Item 476)
- Wright, Capt. R. Military payroll of Captain R. Wright's Company of Colonel James Livingston's Battalion, 1779 May (Box 3, Item 478)
- Pye, David. Certification of Disbursements by Daniel Gerow as executor of the Rynier House Estate, 1779 May 3 (Box 3, Item 475)
- Clinton, George. Draft of letter. Poughkeepsie, 1779 May 13 (Box 1, Item 143)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Regarding expedition against Indians.
- Clinton, General George. Letter to Colonel Wadsworth. Poughkeepsie, 1779 May 15 (Box 4, Item 533)
  Regarding flour for the army.
- Clinton, George. Letter to Major General McDougall. Poughkeepsie, 1779 May 26 (Box 6, Item 629)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Letter regarding ordering other brigades to strengthen the troops under his command.
- Tappen, Teunis, Jr. Statement that Benjamin Gerow is Delivered to Care of Father. Commission for Conspiracies. Poughkeepsie, 1779 May 27 (Box 6, Item 634)
- Whiting, Colonel Samuel, Lieutenant Colonel 5th Connecticut Line. Letter to Colonel Increase Moseley. Woodbury, 1779 May 31 (Box 3, Item 407)
  Regarding western towns soon being attacked by the enemy.
- McDougall, Alexander. Letter. Continental Village, 1779 June 1 (Box 1, Item 46)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Regarding moving stores.
- Fish, Nicholas. Letter to Varick (?). Camp Shades of Death, 1779 June 11 (Box 2, Item 200)
  Written while on Sullivan's Expedition.
- Platt, Richard, Major and ADC to General McDougall. Letter to Captain Lewis, commanding Lady Washington Galley, 1779 June 19 (Box 3, Item 404)
  Letter stating they were put on board John Peterson and cannot go ashore.
- Van Deusen, John. Letter to Captain Mathew Dederick. Hurley, 1779 June 22 (Box 3, Item 338)
  Regarding payment for ammunition.
- Harrison, Robert H. Letter to the Commanders at Camp in the Clove. New Windsor, 1779 June 28 (Box 1, Item 135)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Request for troops to be amply supplied.
- Worthington, Asa. Letter to Daniel Kellogg or Ebenezer Foote. Fishkill, 1779 June 29 (Box 2, Item 245)
  Regarding pay for pasturing cattle.
- Van Rennselaer, Peter. Military payroll of Captain Peter Van Rensselaer's Company of Colonel James Livingston's Battalion, 1779 July (Box 3, Item 479)
- Barber, Colonel Francis. Letter to wife, Nancy. Wyoming, 1779 July 5 (Box 3, Item 376)
- Clinton, George. Letter to Mrs. Colo. Barber. Poughkeepsie, 1779 July 10 (Box 2, Item 196)
- Platt, Richard. Letter to Captain Lewis, 1779 July 15 (Box 3, Item 308)
- Cramahe, Lieutenant Governor. Pay order for Joseph Dugust. Quebec, 1779 July 16 (Box 3, Item 422)
- Viller, Cornelius. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. Fishkill, 1779 July 23 (Box 5, Item 585)
- Croghan, William. Letter. Smith's Cove, 1779 July 31 (Box 3, Item 413)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Letter stating Virginia Line is stationed and commanded by Lord Stirling; remaining army near West Point.
- Clinton, George. Letter. Poughkeepsie, 1779 August 4 (Box 2, Item 296)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Regarding forwarding letter.
- Meade, R.K. Letter to General Knox, 1779 August 10 (Box 1, Item 136)
  Soldier wishes to enlist.
- Heath, General William. Letter to Lieutenant Colonel Gray. Mandaville, 1779 August 12 (Box 3, Item 309)
  Letter saying by order of General Washington, return to place.
- Deming, Colonel Julius. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. Colchester, 1779 August 13 (Box 5, Item 586)
  Regarding cattle for Hudson River troops.
- Deming, Colonel Julius. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. Colchester, 1779 August 13 (Box 5, Item 587)
- Wayne, Brig. General Anthony. Report of the Light Infantry Piquett Guards, 1779 August 18 (Box 3, Item 301)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Regarding patrol from Fort Clinton to Doodletown.
- Clinton, Sir. Henry. Commission of ensign Richard Dodgson, 1779 September 10 (Box 1, Item 50)
- Wayne, Brigadier General Anthony. Letter to Captain of Clements Guard. Fort Montgomery, 1779 September 21 (Box 3, Item 302)
- Lush, Major. Letter to Colonel Jacobus Bruyn. Kingston, 1779 September 22 (Box 2, Item 233)
- Hobart, John Sloss. Letter to Governor George Clinton. Kingston, 1779 October 16 (Box 2, Item 193)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Regarding resignation.
- Livingston, Robert. Letter to Philip Van Rensselaer. Manor Livingston, 1779 October 17 (Box 3, Item 313)
  Regarding iron bars.
- Adam, John, D.C. Prisoners. Letter to Lewis Pintard, Esq. Elizabeth Town, 1779 November 26 (Box 1, Item 41)
  Regarding provisions for prisoners.
- Hay, Colonel Udny, DQMG. Letter to John Fisher. Fishkill, 1779 December 1 (Box 3, Item 403)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Includes letter from Colonel Petit regarding general account of expenditures.
- Hay, Col. Udny, DQMG. Letter to John Fisher. Fishkill, 1779 December 24 (Box 3, Item 416)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Regarding marquees and tents.
- Frost, William. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. West Point, 1779 December 25 (Box 5, Item 590)
- George III. Act to Discontinue Duty on American Cotton. London, 1779 (Box 3, Item 434)
- Belding, S., AQM. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. Mandaville, 1780 January 15 (Box 3, Item 316)
  Regarding shipment of cattle.
- Cartwright, Thomas, aide de camp to General William Heath. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. Headquarters Highlands, 1780 January 21 (Box 3, Item 370)
  Letter stating parties on the line suffer from want of provisions.
- Deming, Julius, Commissary. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. Hartford, 1780 January 26 (Box 4, Item 547)
  Regarding money for drovers.
- Harding, Joshua. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. Camp Highlands, 1780 January 30 (Box 4, Item 545)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Regarding cattle.
- Ten Eyck, Catherine (Kitty). Letter to Captain John Fisher. Half Moon, 1780 February 22 (Box 2, Item 275)
  Regarding forwarding a shipment to nephew.
- Lansing, John. Receipt. Albany, 1780 February 25 (Box 2, Item 206)
- Frost, William. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. West Point, 1780 February 27 (Box 1, Item 100)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Regarding sheep and cattle.
- Marshall, S.B. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. Fort Arnold, 1780 February 27 (Box 3, Item 317)
  Regarding hiring a butcher.
- Hathorn, John. Certification of account of expenses as NYS representative for 1779, 1780 March 7 (Box 3, Item 310)
- Wadsworth, Finn. Order to pay Major Benjamin Talmage 2000 pounds, 1780 March 9 (Box 1, Item 62)
- Loudon, Samuel. Letter to Managers of the US Lottery, Philadelphia. Fishkill, 1780 April 1 (Box 2, Item 286)
  Regarding unsold tickets.
- Cunningham, William. Report of prisoners confined in the provost near Charlestown, 1780 April 1 (Box 3, Item 426)
- Worthington, Asa. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. Morris Town, 1780 April 30 (Box 3, Item 371)
  Regarding uncertain future employment.
- Coe, John and Gilbert Cooper, Commanders of Sequestration. Cakiatt, 1780 May 2 (Box 3, Item 474)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Letter orders to allow Daniel Gerow to move women and children towards New York.
- Commander-in-Chief. Extract of Letter. Headquarters, Preakness, 1780 May 4 (Box 1, Item 137)
  States that transports are ready to sail.
- Whiting, Rev. Officer Timothy. Letter to John Fisher. West Point, 1780 June 17 (Box 3, Item 391)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Regarding supplies.
- Clinton, Henry. State of Second Battalion, 80th Regiment of HIghlanders commanded by Colonel Henry Clinton, 1780 June 24 (Box 4, Item 508)
- Silliman, B. Gen. S. Letter to Colonel Joseph Moseley. Fairfield, 1780 June 27 (Box 1, Item 33)
  States that the enemy is in motion at West Point.
- Smith, Joseph. Memorandum to Archibald Stewart, Esq. to order 6 boxes of horse shoes, 1780 June 29 (Box 2, Item 256)
- Smith, Joseph. Order to Mr. John Fisher, clothier. Fishkill, 1780 July 7 (Box 2, Item 257)
- Shurkitt, Joseph. Letter to John Fisher. Fishkill, 1780 July 8 (Box 2, Item 273)
  Regarding Marquis' baggage.
- Fiero, Christian. Letter to Captain Dederick. Kaatsbaan, 1780 July 10 (Box 3, Item 341)
  Agreement of Seventh Class with payment.
- Worthington, Asa. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. Camp Jersey, 1780 July 25 (Box 3, Item 368)
- Clarkson, Major M. Letter to Sir Henry Clinton, 1780 July 28 (Box 1, Item 125)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Regarding prisoners.
- Oswald, Eleazer. Letter to Major General Arnold. Baltimore, 1780 August 12 (Box 3, Item 312)
  Regarding conveyance of portmanteau.
- Foote, Ebenezer. Account with Henry Campion, Jr., 1780 August 15-1782 February 12 (Box 4, Item 539)
- Stevens, Nathaniel. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. Fishkill, 1780 August 18 (Box 4, Item 554)
- Schuyler, Philip. Letter to George Clinton. Bergen County near the Liberty Pole, 1780 August 28 (Box 3, Item 383)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Regarding protection of northern and western frontiers of New York.
- Townsend, Ebenezer. Letter to Major General Arnold. New Haven, 1780 August 30 (Box 3, Item 346)
  Regarding matter of house.
- Cunningham, William. Return of Necessarys Wanting for Soliders in the Provost. New York, 1780 August 31 (Box 3, Item 428)
- Worthington, Asa. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. Scrawlingburgh, 1780 September 1 (Box 3, Item 367)
- Townsend, Ebenezer. Letter to Major General Arnold. New Haven, 1780 September 2 (Box 3, Item 347)
  Stating matter of house will rest at present.
- Mansfield, Betsey. Letter to Benedict Arnold. New Haven, 1780 September 2 (Box 3, Item 386)
- Travis, Gilbert and Gabriel Carrisan. Warrant for pasturing cattle. West Chester County, 1780 September 13 (Box 4, Item 540)
- Waltrous, Daniel. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. West Point, 1780 September 22 (Box 1, Item 105)
- Stafford, John R. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. West Point, 1780 September 23 (Box 1, Item 101)
- Account of expenses, 1780 September 3-30 (Box 4, Item 538)
- Dodge, Samuel, Daniel Graham and John Hathorn, Commissioners of Forfeiture in the Middle District of New York. Letter to State Treasurer, 1780 October 4 (Box 4, Item 529)
  Regarding the sale of the estate of Malcolm Morrison.
- Betts, William, AQM. Letter to Mr. Pickles or Mr. Bunson. Fishkill, 1780 October 4 (Box 4, Item 543)
  Regarding pasturing.
- Waltrous, Daniel. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. West Point, 1780 October 8 (Box 4, Item 553)
- Eustis, William. Letter to Gen. Greene Robinson's house, 1780 October 13 (Box 1, Item 11)
- Campbell, Colin. Printed draft to Messrs. Allan Marlar & Co., merchants in London for 140 pounds. New York, N.Y., 1780 October 14 (Box 1, Item 28)
- Worthington, Asa. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. Camp Preakness, 1780 October 18 (Box 3, Item 366)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Regarding cattle for Pennsylvania troops.
- Deming, Julius, Commissary. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. Colchester, 1780 October 20 (Box 4, Item 546)
- Weed, Jacob. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. West Point, 1780 October 25 (Box 1, Item 102)
- Worthington, Asa. Letter to Ebenezer Foote, 1780 October 28 (Box 3, Item 369)
  Letter containing compliments to Miss Brett.
- Worthington, Asa. Letter to Ebenezer Foote, 1780 October 29 (Box 3, Item 364)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Regarding danger of cowboys.
- Britt, Theodorus. Letter to John Fisher, 1780 November (Box 2, Item 268)
- Hughes, Hugh and Thomas Dubois. Articles of Agreement, 1780 November 4 (Box 2, Item 279)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Regarding order for lyme.
- Worthington, Asa. Letter to Ebenezer Foote and Colonel Griffins, 1780 November 5 (Box 3, Item 319)
  Regarding shipment of chest.
- Clinton, George. Letter to Mr. Nicholas Quakenboss, ADQMG. Poughkeepsie, 1780 November 9 (Box 3, Item 358)
  Letter says to deliver letter to General Tenbroeck. Also is regarding purchase of wood and coal.
- Waltrous, Daniel. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. West Point, NY, 1780 November 15 (Box 4, Item 541)
  Asking for more cattle for soldiers.
- Schenck, Henry. Letter to John Fisher., 1780 November 17 (Box 2, Item 272)
  Regarding furnishing a boat.
- Watrous, Daniel. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. West Point, 1780 November 19 (Box 1, Item 103)
- French, Edward. Letter to Paymaster of Col. Wesson's Regiment. Camp at Totowaw, 1780 November 23 (Box 2, Item 190)
  Regarding payment of Matthew Hobbs.
- Watrous, Daniel. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. West Point, 1780 November 29 (Box 1, Item 104)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Regarding cattle on hand.
- Worthington, Asa, QMG. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. Van Duzers Tavern, 4 miles from New Windsor, 1780 November 30 (Box 3, Item 318)
  Regarding cattle shipment.
- Worthington, Asa. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. West Point, 1780 December (Box 3, Item 363)
  Letter states that troops will suffer for meat.
- Worthington, Asa. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. Newburgh, 1780 December 7 (Box 3, Item 365)
  Topics including slaughtering cattle and no Thanksgiving.
- Bell, William, AQM. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. Camp, 1780 December 10 (Box 4, Item 544)
- Adam, John, Comm. of Prisoners. Permission for William Philips on parole to pass to Goshen, New York, 1780 December 13 (Box 2, Item 188)
- Worthington, Asa, Esq. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. West Point, NY, 1780 December 21 (Box 1, Item 34)
- Worthington, Asa. Letter to Ebenezer Foote, 1780 December 24 (Box 3, Item 362)
  Regarding fur for vest.
- Blaine, Col. E. Letter to E. Foote. Newburgh, 1780 December 31 (Box 3, Item 361)
  Regarding stolen cattle.
- Vosburgh, Peter J. Payroll of Peter Vosburgh's Company for Aug-Oct of 1780 (Box 2, Item 180)
  List of men, ranks, and salaries.
- Dederick, Capt. Matthew. Bill, 1780 (Box 3, Item 342)
- Forsyth, James. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. Continental Village, 1780 (Box 4, Item 549)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Regarding butchers.
- Clinton, James. Letter to wife, Mary Dewitt Clinton. Albany, 1781 January 6 (Box 3, Item 378)
- Todd, John. Petition to the Supreme Court of the State of New York. Albany, N.Y., 1781 January 16 (Box 1, Item 7)
  Indictment of High Treason.
- Willse, Martin. Letter to Mr. John Fisher. Fishkill Landing, 1781 February 14 (Box 2, Item 264)
- Glumy, Lt. William. Discharge for Corporal Dalemer, 1781 February 16 (Box 2, Item 189)
- Laurance, John. Letter to George Washington at New Windsor. Peekskill, 1781 February 20 (Box 1, Item 138)
  Letter states "must decline offer."
- Gordon, David. Printed draft to Thomas Harley and Henry Drummond, London for 100 pounds. New York, N.Y., 1781 March (Box 1, Item 29)
- Clinton, George, Governor of New York. Governor's Protest against Arthur Parks, Esq. taking seat in Council of Appointments. Albany, 1781 March 29 (Box 4, Item 534)
- Clinton, George. Letter to Mr. Nicholas Quakenboss, ADQMG. Poughkeepsie, 1781 April 2 (Box 3, Item 359)
  Regarding troop provisions.
- Heath, William. Letter to Governor George Clinton and Draft of Clinton's Reply. At Garrison, West Point, 1781 April 29 (Box 3, Item 429)
  List of families to go to New York.
- Hughes, Colonel. Order for items including axes, salt, knapsacks, 1781 May (Box 2, Item 266)
- George III. Warrant to pay Henry Earl of Pembroke, 1781 May 25 (Box 2, Item 176)
- Meng, Christopher, storekeeper. Letter to Mr. Fisher. Newburgh, 1781 May 29 (Box 1, Item 6)
- Humphrys, Lieutenant Colonel David. Letter to Colonel Wadsworth. Headquarters, New Windsor, 1781 May 31 (Box 3, Item 331)
  Payment of interest on state notes.
- Slauson, David. Plan of homelands of Mr. David Slauson. Fairfield County, 1781 June 2 (Box 5, Item 571)
- Knox, Henry. Letter to Colonel Shepard. New Windsor, 1781 June 3 (Box 1, Item 52)
  Regarding movement of stores.
- Stirling, William Alexander (Lord). Letter to Colonel Pickering. New Windsor, 1781 June 5 (Box 3, Item 387)
  Regarding a saddled horse.
- Pickering, Colonel Timothy. Order to Mr. John Fisher. Quartermaster General's Office, 1781 June 17 (Box 2, Item 267)
  Advises ordering a craft large enough to carry boards mentioned in enclosed order.
- Smith, Melancton. Letter to Commrs of Sequestration for Dutchess County. Bill for summoning a jury, 1781 June 24 (Box 1, Item 97)
- Meng, Christopher, storekeeper. Letter to Mr. Fisher. Newburgh, 1781 June 26 (Box 1, Item 58)
- Smith, William, oarmaker. Message to Mr. Fisher at the Land, 1781 July (Box 2, Item 261)
- Clinton, George. Letter to Nicholas Quackenboss. Poughkeepsie, 1781 July 6 (Box 2, Item 284)
  Regarding phaeton order from James Bloodgood.
- McCalister, Archibald. Letter to T.S. Lee, Esq., Governor of Maryland. Annapolis, 1781 July 10 (Box 1, Item 116)
  Regarding payment for service in Regiment of Continental Troops belonging to Maryland.
- Adams, William. Letter to Colonel Increase Moseley. Tousey's Tavern, 1781 July 15 (Box 3, Item 425)
  Regarding supplies.
- Smith, William, oarmaker. Invoice. Fishkill Landing, 1781 August 3 (Box 2, Item 260)
- Carter, John. Financial Agreement with Jeremiah Wadsworth. Phillipsburgh, Headquarters of the Allied Army of America and France, 1781 August 18 (Box 3, Item 311)
  Regarding settlement of accounts.
- Sutherland, Captain Alexander. Account of Subsistence for the 2nd Battalion, 71st Regiment, 1781 August 25-October 24 (Box 4, Item 509)
- Tillinghass, Charles. Letter and invoice to John Fisher. Camp, 1781 September 16 (Box 5, Item 592)
- Stirling, William Alexander, Lord. Letter to Thomas F. Jackson, Stirling's Aide de Camp. Peeskill, 1781 September 17 (Box 3, Item 333)
  Regarding five gallons of Madeira.
- Van Cortlandt, Pierre, Lieutenant Governor of NY. Permit to allow passage of John Brown. Peekskill, 1781 September 30 (Box 3, Item 329)
- Mills, Elisha. Receipt for transporting provisions, 1781 October (Box 2, Item 254)
- Wistar, John and Charlotte Newbold of Mansfield, Burlington County, NJ. Quaker Marriage Intention. Facsimile, 1781 October 17 (Box 5, Item 610)
- Britt, Doris. Letter to John Fisher, 1781 November (Box 2, Item 271)
- Clinton, George. Letter to Captain Israel Honeywell. Poughkeepsie, 1781 November 10 (Box 3, Item 379)
  Regarding keeping hogs and forage from falling into hands of enemy in West Chester County.
- Delancey, General Oliver. Letter, 1781 November 22 (Box 2, Item 194)
- Eagle Glass Works. 5 Dollar Order by Jason Smith. Port Elizabeth, NJ, 1781 December 14 (Box 3, Item 451)
- Lincoln, Benjamin. Order to Commissaries regarding provisions. War Office, 1781 December 22 (Box 2, Item 290)
- Stevens, Nathaniel. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. Order for delivery of cattle to Comfort Sands & his Company. Fishkill, 1781 December 29 (Box 3, Item 432)
- Sands, Comfort. Letter to unknown, 1781 December 31 (Box 1, Item 99)
  Regarding order for cattle.
- Den, John. Order of Ejectment for Richard Fen, names Moses Gomez, 1782 January 3 (Box 1, Item 126)
- Slason, Capt. Nathaniel. Pay voucher. State of Connecticut, 1782 February 7 (Box 1, Item 112)
  Printed and signed by William Moseley and Finn Wadsworth, Committee.
- Wilber, Martin. Letter to Mr. John Fisher. Landing, 1782 February 10 (Box 2, Item 278)
  Regarding stolen goods.
- Heath, William. Letter to Brigadier General Hand. Headquarters Highland, 1782 February 13 (Box 3, Item 430)
  Mr. McEvoy confined and sent to Philadelphia.
- Livingston, William S. Letter to His Excellency. Acquaquanock, 1782 April 15 (Box 1, Item 54)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Regarding two men and six horses captured making their way from New York to Philadelphia.
- Fisher, John. Letter to Henry Johnson. Fishkill Landing, 1782 April 20 (Box 2, Item 276)
  Regarding order for hay.
- Clinton, George. Letter to Col. Willet. Poughkeepsie, 1782 May 4 (Box 3, Item 401)
  Regarding appointment of Major Finck.
- Tillinghass, Chas. Letter to John Fisher. Fishkill, 1782 May 9 (Box 2, Item 265)
- Connecticut Treasury Note to Mr. Simeon Parsons for 19 pounds, 1782 June 1 (Box 2, Item 183)
- Colt, Peter, Treasurer of State of Connecticut. War service pay for Mr. Bryant Horman, 1782 June 1 (Box 5, Item 594)
- Norwood, Richard. Letter to John Fisher, 1782 June 14 (Box 2, Item 274)
  Regarding files.
- Tillinghass, Chas. Letter to John Fisher. Fishkill, 1782 June 14 (Box 2, Item 277)
  Request for wire.
- Hughes, Hugh, DQM. Letter to John Fisher. Fishkill, 1782 June 24 (Box 2, Item 262)
- Clinton, George. Letter to Gerard Bancker, 1782 July 3 (Box 3, Item 402)
  Regarding accounting.
- Palmer, John and Josiah Brackett. Certificate of weight of coils. Fishkill Landing, 1782 August 5 (Box 2, Item 270)
- Pickering, Timothy. Letter to Mr. John Fisher. New Windsor, 1782 August 24 (Box 1, Item 12)
- Fisher, John, ADQM. Certificate of adequate fuel supply. Fishkill Landing, 1782 August 25 (Box 2, Item 269)
- Pickering, Timothy. Letter to John Fisher, 1782 August 28 (Box 3, Item 417)
  Regarding need for painters.
- Pickering, Timothy. Note to Quartermaster, 3 Brigade Massachusetts. New Windsor, 1782 August 29 (Box 1, Item 5)
- Willett, Marinus of New York. Letter to Hon. Major Gen. Lord Stirling. Albany, N.Y., 1782 September 16 (Box 1, Item 4)
- Stewart, Charles. Letter to Mr. Hubbard. Verplanks Point, 1782 October 21 (Box 2, Item 202)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Regarding drove of cattle.